[{"question": "M\u0113dus ad~. D\u0101vus abest.", "answer": "M\u0113dus adest. D\u0101vus abest.", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus adest. D\u0101vus abest.", "perplexity": 68.33613586425781}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus ad\u012b. D\u0101vus abest.", "perplexity": 181.52859497070312}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus ad\u0113. D\u0101vus abest.", "perplexity": 189.98939514160156}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus ad\u0101. D\u0101vus abest.", "perplexity": 195.16561889648438}]}, {"question": "M\u0113dus adest. D\u0101vus ab~.", "answer": "M\u0113dus adest. D\u0101vus abest.", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus adest. D\u0101vus abest.", "perplexity": 68.33609771728516}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus adest. D\u0101vus ab\u0101.", "perplexity": 238.00823974609375}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus adest. D\u0101vus ab\u0113.", "perplexity": 212.00094604492188}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus adest. D\u0101vus abat.", "perplexity": 138.623046875}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius imper~ : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "answer": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "perplexity": 121.32598114013672}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imperet : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "perplexity": 144.63621520996094}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imper\u0101 : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "perplexity": 205.75994873046875}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imper\u0113 : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "perplexity": 263.556640625}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc~ D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "answer": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "perplexity": 121.32598114013672}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u012b D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "perplexity": 132.80345153808594}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0113 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "perplexity": 112.3407974243164}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Vocat D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "perplexity": 103.52991485595703}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113d~!\"", "answer": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113de!\"", "perplexity": 121.32604217529297}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113det!\"", "perplexity": 111.212890625}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113dat!\"", "perplexity": 129.5572509765625}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius imperat : \"Voc\u0101 D\u0101vum, M\u0113d\u0101!\"", "perplexity": 89.9947280883789}]}, {"question": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum voc~ : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u012b!\"", "answer": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u012b!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 23.24768829345703}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocest : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 64.74175262451172}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum voc\u0101 : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 50.41278076171875}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum voc\u0113 : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 68.10828399658203}]}, {"question": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101v~! Ven\u012b!\"", "answer": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u012b!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 23.247697830200195}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101v\u012b! Ven\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 24.36077117919922}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101v\u0113! Ven\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 25.396055221557617}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101v\u0101! Ven\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 28.04082679748535}]}, {"question": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101ve! Ven~!\"", "answer": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u012b!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 23.247697830200195}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101ve! Venest!\"", "perplexity": 44.86037063598633}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u0101!\"", "perplexity": 31.063365936279297}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus D\u0101vum vocat : \"D\u0101ve! Ven\u0113!\"", "perplexity": 28.291603088378906}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus ven~ neque I\u016blium videt.", "answer": "D\u0101vus venit neque I\u016blium videt.", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus venit neque I\u016blium videt.", "perplexity": 40.863529205322266}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus ven\u012b neque I\u016blium videt.", "perplexity": 94.9322509765625}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus ven\u0113 neque I\u016blium videt.", "perplexity": 130.33258056640625}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus ven\u0101 neque I\u016blium videt.", "perplexity": 167.78094482421875}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus venit neque I\u016blium vid~.", "answer": "D\u0101vus venit neque I\u016blium videt.", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus venit neque I\u016blium videt.", "perplexity": 40.86355972290039}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus venit neque I\u016blium videst.", "perplexity": 87.92672729492188}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus venit neque I\u016blium vid\u0101.", "perplexity": 260.0926818847656}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus venit neque I\u016blium vid\u0113.", "perplexity": 132.67572021484375}]}, {"question": "M\u0113dus: \"Sal\u016bt~ dominum!\"", "answer": "M\u0113dus: \"Sal\u016bt\u0101 dominum!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus: \"Sal\u016bt\u0101 dominum!\"", "perplexity": 100.93879699707031}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus: \"Sal\u016bt\u012b dominum!\"", "perplexity": 93.53679656982422}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus: \"Sal\u016bt\u0113 dominum!\"", "perplexity": 115.81092071533203}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus: \"Sal\u016btat dominum!\"", "perplexity": 151.82614135742188}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016bt~ : \"Salv\u0113, domine! Quid est?\"", "answer": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016btat : \"Salv\u0113, domine! Quid est?\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016btat : \"Salv\u0113, domine! Quid est?\"", "perplexity": 31.959346771240234}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016btet : \"Salv\u0113, domine! Quid est?\"", "perplexity": 30.4700870513916}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016bt\u0101 : \"Salv\u0113, domine! Quid est?\"", "perplexity": 32.828826904296875}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016bt\u0113 : \"Salv\u0113, domine! Quid est?\"", "perplexity": 39.47624969482422}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016btat : \"Salv\u0113, domin~! Quid est?\"", "answer": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016btat : \"Salv\u0113, domine! Quid est?\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016btat : \"Salv\u0113, domine! Quid est?\"", "perplexity": 31.959362030029297}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016btat : \"Salv\u0113, domin\u012b! Quid est?\"", "perplexity": 40.17423629760742}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016btat : \"Salv\u0113, domin\u0113! Quid est?\"", "perplexity": 45.49938201904297}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus dominum sal\u016btat : \"Salv\u0113, domin\u0101! Quid est?\"", "perplexity": 44.40528869628906}]}, {"question": "Dominus: \"Tac~, serve! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "answer": "Dominus: \"Tac\u0113, serve! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "Dominus: \"Tac\u0113, serve! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "perplexity": 88.61854553222656}, {"evalsentence": "Dominus: \"Tacest, serve! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "perplexity": 133.90325927734375}, {"evalsentence": "Dominus: \"Tac\u0101, serve! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "perplexity": 97.74385070800781}, {"evalsentence": "Dominus: \"Tacat, serve! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "perplexity": 129.82025146484375}]}, {"question": "Dominus: \"Tac\u0113, serv~! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "answer": "Dominus: \"Tac\u0113, serve! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "Dominus: \"Tac\u0113, serve! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "perplexity": 88.61849975585938}, {"evalsentence": "Dominus: \"Tac\u0113, servet! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "perplexity": 110.72058868408203}, {"evalsentence": "Dominus: \"Tac\u0113, servat! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "perplexity": 113.55652618408203}, {"evalsentence": "Dominus: \"Tac\u0113, serv\u0101! Numm\u012b me\u012b ubi sunt?\"", "perplexity": 89.93805694580078}]}, {"question": "Servus tac~ neque respondet.", "answer": "Servus tacet neque respondet.", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "Servus tacet neque respondet.", "perplexity": 20.731708526611328}, {"evalsentence": "Servus tacest neque respondet.", "perplexity": 70.760009765625}, {"evalsentence": "Servus tac\u0101 neque respondet.", "perplexity": 136.3410186767578}, {"evalsentence": "Servus tac\u0113 neque respondet.", "perplexity": 99.79374694824219}]}, {"question": "Servus tacet neque respond~.", "answer": "Servus tacet neque respondet.", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "Servus tacet neque respondet.", "perplexity": 20.731698989868164}, {"evalsentence": "Servus tacet neque respond\u012b.", "perplexity": 130.13449096679688}, {"evalsentence": "Servus tacet neque respond\u0113.", "perplexity": 111.56275177001953}, {"evalsentence": "Servus tacet neque respond\u0101.", "perplexity": 202.6647186279297}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius: \"Respond~!\"", "answer": "I\u016blius: \"Respond\u0113!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"Respond\u0113!\"", "perplexity": 66.10936737060547}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"Respondest!\"", "perplexity": 76.8051986694336}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"Respond\u0101!\"", "perplexity": 89.72012329101562}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"Respondat!\"", "perplexity": 50.08940505981445}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus: \"Interrog~ M\u0113dum!\"", "answer": "D\u0101vus: \"Interrog\u0101 M\u0113dum!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Interrog\u0101 M\u0113dum!\"", "perplexity": 69.07687377929688}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Interroget M\u0113dum!\"", "perplexity": 108.17070770263672}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Interrogat M\u0113dum!\"", "perplexity": 73.14632415771484}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Interrog\u0113 M\u0113dum!\"", "perplexity": 101.40375518798828}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrog~ : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113de?\"", "answer": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrogat : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113de?\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrogat : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113de?\"", "perplexity": 33.35870361328125}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrog\u012b : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113de?\"", "perplexity": 80.402587890625}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrog\u0113 : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113de?\"", "perplexity": 77.41124725341797}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrog\u0101 : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113de?\"", "perplexity": 63.19700622558594}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrogat : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113d~?\"", "answer": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrogat : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113de?\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrogat : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113de?\"", "perplexity": 33.358680725097656}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrogat : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113dest?\"", "perplexity": 45.52720260620117}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrogat : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113d\u0101?\"", "perplexity": 30.585689544677734}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius M\u0113dum interrogat : \"Ubi est pec\u016bnia mea, M\u0113d\u0113?\"", "perplexity": 29.571441650390625}]}, {"question": "M\u0113dus: \"D\u0101vus pec\u016bniam tuam hab~.\"", "answer": "M\u0113dus: \"D\u0101vus pec\u016bniam tuam habet.\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus: \"D\u0101vus pec\u016bniam tuam habet.\"", "perplexity": 36.68003845214844}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus: \"D\u0101vus pec\u016bniam tuam hab\u012b.\"", "perplexity": 132.79718017578125}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus: \"D\u0101vus pec\u016bniam tuam hab\u0113.\"", "perplexity": 88.51988983154297}, {"evalsentence": "M\u0113dus: \"D\u0101vus pec\u016bniam tuam hab\u0101.\"", "perplexity": 156.41685485839844}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dn~ sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101ve!\"", "answer": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dne sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101ve!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dne sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101ve!\"", "perplexity": 50.98357391357422}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dnest sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101ve!\"", "perplexity": 76.8777847290039}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dn\u0101 sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101ve!\"", "perplexity": 49.642433166503906}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dn\u0113 sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101ve!\"", "perplexity": 44.78956604003906}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dne sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101v~!\"", "answer": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dne sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101ve!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dne sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101ve!\"", "perplexity": 50.98360061645508}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dne sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101v\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 44.68984603881836}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dne sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101v\u0113!\"", "perplexity": 52.72373580932617}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"P\u014dne sacculum tuum in m\u0113ns\u0101, D\u0101v\u0101!\"", "perplexity": 56.9567985534668}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus p\u0101r~ : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dnit.", "answer": "D\u0101vus p\u0101ret : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dnit.", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus p\u0101ret : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dnit.", "perplexity": 66.21578216552734}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus p\u0101rest : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dnit.", "perplexity": 82.96611022949219}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus p\u0101r\u0101 : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dnit.", "perplexity": 62.286808013916016}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus p\u0101r\u0113 : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dnit.", "perplexity": 62.593833923339844}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus p\u0101ret : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dn~.", "answer": "D\u0101vus p\u0101ret : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dnit.", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus p\u0101ret : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dnit.", "perplexity": 66.21578216552734}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus p\u0101ret : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dn\u012b.", "perplexity": 89.02946472167969}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus p\u0101ret : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dn\u0113.", "perplexity": 91.89552307128906}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus p\u0101ret : sacculum suum in m\u0113ns\u0101 p\u014dn\u0101.", "perplexity": 107.67507934570312}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus: \"Vid~, domine : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "answer": "D\u0101vus: \"Vid\u0113, domine : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Vid\u0113, domine : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "perplexity": 18.065420150756836}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Videst, domine : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "perplexity": 24.478424072265625}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Vid\u0101, domine : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "perplexity": 27.2388973236084}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Vidat, domine : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "perplexity": 26.124744415283203}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus: \"Vid\u0113, domin~ : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "answer": "D\u0101vus: \"Vid\u0113, domine : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Vid\u0113, domine : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "perplexity": 18.0654239654541}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Vid\u0113, dominet : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "perplexity": 29.53718376159668}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Vid\u0113, dominat : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "perplexity": 30.72473907470703}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus: \"Vid\u0113, domin\u0101 : sacculus meus vacuus est.\"", "perplexity": 21.02118682861328}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bm~ sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "answer": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "perplexity": 75.2901382446289}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bmest sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "perplexity": 91.61991882324219}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bm\u0101 sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "perplexity": 72.7521743774414}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bm\u0113 sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "perplexity": 76.35863494873047}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113d~, bone serve!\"", "answer": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "perplexity": 75.29017639160156}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113d\u012b, bone serve!\"", "perplexity": 58.93831253051758}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113d\u0113, bone serve!\"", "perplexity": 62.53902816772461}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113d\u0101, bone serve!\"", "perplexity": 63.714900970458984}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bon~ serve!\"", "answer": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "perplexity": 75.2901382446289}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bonest serve!\"", "perplexity": 152.68711853027344}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bon\u0101 serve!\"", "perplexity": 101.0622329711914}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bon\u0113 serve!\"", "perplexity": 101.89868927001953}]}, {"question": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serv~!\"", "answer": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serve!\"", "perplexity": 75.29017639160156}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serv\u012b!\"", "perplexity": 88.694091796875}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serv\u0113!\"", "perplexity": 98.37381744384766}, {"evalsentence": "I\u016blius: \"S\u016bme sacculum tuum et disc\u0113de, bone serv\u0101!\"", "perplexity": 99.86743927001953}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bm~ et disc\u0113dit.", "answer": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bmit et disc\u0113dit.", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bmit et disc\u0113dit.", "perplexity": 75.50196075439453}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bmest et disc\u0113dit.", "perplexity": 74.0998306274414}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bm\u0101 et disc\u0113dit.", "perplexity": 109.5492172241211}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bm\u0113 et disc\u0113dit.", "perplexity": 111.60462188720703}]}, {"question": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bmit et disc\u0113d~.", "answer": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bmit et disc\u0113dit.", "evalsentences": [{"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bmit et disc\u0113dit.", "perplexity": 75.50203704833984}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bmit et disc\u0113d\u012b.", "perplexity": 69.60991668701172}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bmit et disc\u0113d\u0113.", "perplexity": 76.53466033935547}, {"evalsentence": "D\u0101vus sacculum suum s\u016bmit et disc\u0113d\u0101.", "perplexity": 98.83987426757812}]}]